<source><job><title><![CDATA[Tele2 Executive Trainee Program 2019 ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, October 4th 2018, 1:35:49 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholms-l%C3%A4n-Tele2-Executive-Trainee-Program-2019/495621901/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>We are on a hunt for exceptionally motivated and fearless candidates to join our Executive Trainee Program 2019!</strong> </p>

<p><strong>This is who you are… </strong></p>

<p>…We are looking for trainees for our new executive leadership team who can help us remain the challenger we’ve always been. You are <strong>fearless </strong>and<strong> open </strong>in your approach with a <strong>cost effective</strong> mindset. We believe that you are <strong>reliable </strong>with high quality and delivery precision in our <strong>flexible </strong>work environment<strong>.</strong><br>
 </p>

<p><strong>To succeed</strong>, you need to think fast and move even faster. You'll need to dig in and do the work without prestige. Take bold initiatives and never hesitate to challenge anything or anyone to see them through. Not even your boss. <br>
 </p>

<p><strong>This is what you have…</strong></p>

<p>A degree in Business, Law, Engineering or IT with proven academic excellence. Experience from relevant extracurricular activities such as student associations and preferably an exchange semester along with professional experience, e.g. internships or a current employment.<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>These are our roles…</strong></p>

<p>…We are recruiting eight trainees for our 2019 program and our new executive team.<br>
 </p>

<p>Executive CEO Trainee<br>
Executive CFO Trainee<br>
Executive CTO Trainee<br>
Executive CIO Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Sweden Consumer Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Sweden Business Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Strategy & Business Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Mobile Network Trainee<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>This is the program....</strong> </p>

<p>….You will get a deep understanding of the Telecom Industry in general and Tele2 in particular, both organizational and strategical. During the program you will take part of both <strong>internal and external training</strong>. We also offer you a <strong>mentor </strong>who will be a great support as he or she is a former trainee, not to mention you will also have an <strong>external coach</strong> to help you develop in your individual defined direction! <br>
 </p>

<p> <strong>This is the job.... </strong></p>

<p>…As a trainee, you will be a part of our one year-long program, based at the Tele2 headquarters in Stockholm. You will work closely with your executive and your fellow trainee colleagues as well as additional Tele2 stakeholders. You will also be given opportunities to participate in other projects throughout the organization. This will give you a great opportunity to create a strong foundation for a successful career within Tele2 and/or the Kinnevik family. <br>
 </p>

<p><strong>Are you curious on what happens after tour trainee year? </strong></p>

<p>We aim to build future Tele2 leaders and therefor after your trainee year we aim to place you in a high professional role within Tele2 or the Kinnevik family. You will have a close relationship with our talent acquisition specialist through your year to assure that your next opportunity at Tele2 will be an exciting challenge.<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>Are you still reading? Good, because the application period is currently open and closes 1 January 2019.</strong></p>

<p>We are currently conducting HR interviews and selections for our <strong>assessment center in January</strong> where the chosen candidates will get the chance to meet our currents trainees, old trainees and our executives for a full day at our award-winning offices in Kista.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Kista]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-495621901-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Tele2 Executive Trainee Program 2019 ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, October 4th 2018, 1:35:49 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholms-l%C3%A4n-Tele2-Executive-Trainee-Program-2019/495621901/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>We are on a hunt for exceptionally motivated and fearless candidates to join our Executive Trainee Program 2019!</strong> </p>

<p><strong>This is who you are… </strong></p>

<p>…We are looking for trainees for our new executive leadership team who can help us remain the challenger we’ve always been. You are <strong>fearless </strong>and<strong> open </strong>in your approach with a <strong>cost effective</strong> mindset. We believe that you are <strong>reliable </strong>with high quality and delivery precision in our <strong>flexible </strong>work environment<strong>.</strong><br>
 </p>

<p><strong>To succeed</strong>, you need to think fast and move even faster. You'll need to dig in and do the work without prestige. Take bold initiatives and never hesitate to challenge anything or anyone to see them through. Not even your boss. <br>
 </p>

<p><strong>This is what you have…</strong></p>

<p>A degree in Business, Law, Engineering or IT with proven academic excellence. Experience from relevant extracurricular activities such as student associations and preferably an exchange semester along with professional experience, e.g. internships or a current employment.<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>These are our roles…</strong></p>

<p>…We are recruiting eight trainees for our 2019 program and our new executive team.<br>
 </p>

<p>Executive CEO Trainee<br>
Executive CFO Trainee<br>
Executive CTO Trainee<br>
Executive CIO Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Sweden Consumer Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Sweden Business Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Strategy & Business Trainee<br>
Executive EVP Mobile Network Trainee<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>This is the program....</strong> </p>

<p>….You will get a deep understanding of the Telecom Industry in general and Tele2 in particular, both organizational and strategical. During the program you will take part of both <strong>internal and external training</strong>. We also offer you a <strong>mentor </strong>who will be a great support as he or she is a former trainee, not to mention you will also have an <strong>external coach</strong> to help you develop in your individual defined direction! <br>
 </p>

<p> <strong>This is the job.... </strong></p>

<p>…As a trainee, you will be a part of our one year-long program, based at the Tele2 headquarters in Stockholm. You will work closely with your executive and your fellow trainee colleagues as well as additional Tele2 stakeholders. You will also be given opportunities to participate in other projects throughout the organization. This will give you a great opportunity to create a strong foundation for a successful career within Tele2 and/or the Kinnevik family. <br>
 </p>

<p><strong>Are you curious on what happens after tour trainee year? </strong></p>

<p>We aim to build future Tele2 leaders and therefor after your trainee year we aim to place you in a high professional role within Tele2 or the Kinnevik family. You will have a close relationship with our talent acquisition specialist through your year to assure that your next opportunity at Tele2 will be an exciting challenge.<br>
 </p>

<p><strong>Are you still reading? Good, because the application period is currently open and closes 1 January 2019.</strong></p>

<p>We are currently conducting HR interviews and selections for our <strong>assessment center in January</strong> where the chosen candidates will get the chance to meet our currents trainees, old trainees and our executives for a full day at our award-winning offices in Kista.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-495621901-ADGEN_TELE2-2]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer - Tech Tribe ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, October 29th 2018, 10:35:33 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Quality-Assurance-Engineer-Tech-Tribe/500583301/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p><br />
The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Quality and Operations unit is responsible for system management and QA within the D&C-domain. The unit is composed of Quality Assurance Engineers, Incident & Problem Managers and DevOps. </p>

<p><br />
<br />
We are looking for a technically skilled Quality Assurance Engineer who doesn’t think great is good enough!<br />
 </p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>As a Quality Assurance Engineer within the Tech Tribe you will work with quality assurance of IT-services both during development and in production. The Tech Tribe’s main responsibility is to develop services for other developers, mainly in the Commercial tribe. The tribe is responsible for coordinating and solving technical & architectural challenges and provide guidance and simplification. In this role you will ensure continuous improvement in both product-quality and in production. Your responsibilities include:<br />
 </p>

<ul>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Manual, exploratory and automated testing</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Managing test data and test environments</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Acting as Quality Specialist in quality refinement and requirement gathering</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Monitor all stages of digital product development to identify and resolve malfunctions</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Owning and implementing a test strategy</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Quality Assurance Engineer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 20 QA Engineers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><br />
<br />
<strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>As a Quality Assurance Engineer within the Tech Tribe you need to be technically skilled, preferably you have experience working as a developer. In this role you are responsible for the digital product quality from start to finish and it is up to you to make sure you are one step ahead. You enjoy responsibility and you are skilled at communicating your ideas to stakeholders. Formal requirements for the role include:<br />
 </p>

<p style="margin-left:48.0px"> </p>

<ul>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">3+ years experience working with Quality Assurance within a digital product</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Experience from test automation</li>
 <li style="margin-left:57.0px">Experience from working in an agile team</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
Working as a Quality Assurance Engineer within the Tech Tribe you will play a key role in one of eight agile teams: Comviq Integration, Residential/Business Integration, Common Capabilities, Commerce, Identity & Auth, ER, Self-Care and DevOps/SRE.<br />
 </p>

<p><br />
<strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong><br />
 </p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-500583301-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Tele2 söker medarbetare till Kundservice B2B Support ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, October 29th 2018, 2:36:23 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Tele2-s%C3%B6ker-medarbetare-till-Kundservice-B2B-Support/500641401/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Jobbar du på en outsourcad kundservice idag och är redo att utvecklas mer? Då har vi den perfekta tjänsten för dig!</p>

<p>Hos oss på Tele2 B2B Kundservice får du möjlighet att arbeta mot våra allra största företagskunder och istället för att skicka vidare ärenden får du själv ta fullt ansvar och fatta egna beslut. Vi erbjuder dig en utvecklande roll och för den som har ambition och vilja finns många spännande karriärmöjligheter inom företaget. De senaste 12 månaderna har ca 30% av våra kundservicemedarbetare gått vidare inom företaget.</p>

<p><strong>Vi erbjuder dig:</strong></p>

<ul>
 <li>Mycket goda karriärmöjligheter – vi utbildar dig och ser till att du blir riktigt vass på det du gör!</li>
 <li>Chefer som värnar om dig och din utveckling – vi arbetar aktivt med feedback och coachning</li>
 <li>Eget ansvar och mandat till att fatta egna beslut</li>
 <li>En fantastisk teamkultur med stor frihet<br />
 </li>
</ul>

<p>Tjänsten är en tillsvidareanställning på heltid med arbetstider under kontorstid måndag–fredag. Tjänsten är placerad på huvudkontoret i Kista.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan!</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Service & Support]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Kista]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-500641401-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend developer - Self-Care squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, October 30th 2018, 10:35:56 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer/500825601/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET Backend developer to the Self-Care squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description</strong></p>

<p>The Self-Care squad enables self-service capabilities to customers that are scalable, accessible and easily deployable. As a Backend developer within this squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a backend developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 .NET Backend developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over your work and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>The Self-Care squad builds new, highly prioritized, central and demanded products within Tele2. In this squad there will always be new challenges - from simple tasks to highly complex architectural solution-oriented tasks.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-500825601-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[UX designer - Commercial tribe ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, October 30th 2018, 12:36:31 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-UX-designer/500851201/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>“We are looking for a curious UX designer who is a firm believer that great design makes people happy!”</p>

<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions.</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong><br />
 </p>

<p>As a UX designer within the Commercial tribe you work to ensure a smooth journey for Tele2’s customers and develop the functionality needed to enable them to perform their required activities. The Tribe is responsible for developing functionality for all the customer lifecycle phases. In this role you work in close collaboration with different stakeholders to ensure a great user experience. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">Develop holistic, high-quality user experience solutions</li>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">Design user experience solutions for a products based on our design strategy and guidelines</li>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">Qualitative/ quantitative research testing and prototyping</li>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">Continues improvements of the user journey</li>
</ul>

<p style="margin-left:48.0px"> </p>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a UX designer within D&C SE you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 13 UX designers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong><br />
 </p>

<p>We are looking for a person who is curious and who is always seeking to improve themselves - as well as the team. You are not afraid to make mistakes but more importantly you are never afraid to ask for help. You love to produce and idea from start to finish and you believe that the details are as important as meeting a deadline. You have a user-centric approach and you are able to articulate “why” you make your decision. Formal requirements include:</p>

<ul>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">2+ years working as a UX Designer</li>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">2+ years’ work experience of Digital Design</li>
 <li style="margin-left:48.0px">Experience working in Sketch, Invision and/or other prototyping tools<br />
 </li>
</ul>

<p>The Commercial tribe is a collection of different agile teams working directly with customer experience for one of these three brands: Comviq, Tele2 Residential and Tele2 Business. As a UX designer within one of these brands your work is highly visible and makes a big impact for all Tele2 customers.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>About Tele2 </strong></p>

<p>Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. Tele2 is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p><br />
The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) takes initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centers divided into areas of technology focus. The areas are integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply with your portfolio and resume by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-500851201-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Residential Join squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Wednesday, October 31st 2018, 11:35:19 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-End-developer-Residential-Join-squad/501209201/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-End developer who wants to deliver world-class user experiences to our customers!</p>

<p><strong>Role description</strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Residential Join squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The Residential Join squad's mission is to optimize the journey to become a Tele2 customer. The squad is responsible for supporting our customers with relevant and clear information and support the launches of different campaigns. In this role you will collaborate closely with other teams when needed. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-End developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The squad is responsible for the first impression and creating a smooth transition to becoming a Tele2 customer. Working as a Front-End developer in the Residential Join squad you will play a crucial part in creating an extraordinary experience for customers which will lead to customer loyalty.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-501209201-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Sales Quality and Operations Manager ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Wednesday, October 31st 2018, 11:34:58 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Sales-Quality-and-Operations-Manager/501209501/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>We’re now looking for a person with e-commerce experience to join our Sales Quality and Operations team!</p>

<p><strong>Role description</strong></p>

<p>As a Sales Quality and Operations Manager you work to improve functionality and experience within the e-commerce platform concerning sales and delivery. You will be responsible for the content and configuration of all products and services within the Tele2 Business web shop. In this role you will coordinate and configure campaigns and products on the website, and you will collaborate with Sales department, Technical Product Owner (TPO), and other stakeholders within the organization to ensure correct products, prices and product information. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Product configuration, planning and implementing requests for both ongoing and new campaigns</li>
 <li>Analysing and optimizing the content within the webpage to maximize the sales and conversion</li>
 <li>Analysing and optimizing the SEO, customer experience and customer satisfaction.</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Your role is roughly composed of 30% strategy and 70% operational tasks. The e-commerce platform used is built in Magento. As a Sales Quality and Operations Manager, you are also a part of a chapter, composed of three individuals with the same role responsible for the other brands: Comviq and Tele2 Residential. The chapter will meet on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a curious and analytic person who always look for improvements. To be successful in this role you must be able to work in a fast-paced environment and be comfortable owning your process from start to finish. You enjoy responsibility and you are skilled at communicating your ideas. Formal requirements include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>2+ years of experience working with e-commerce</li>
 <li>Experience working in Magento</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>As a Sales Quality and Operations Manager within the Tele2 Business brand your work will be highly visible and make a big impact on the profitability, sales growth and customer satisfaction.</p>

<p><strong>About Tele2</strong></p>

<p><br />
Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. Tele2 is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p><br />
The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centers divided into areas of technology focus. The areas are integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.<br />
 </p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-501209501-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Scrum Master - Commercial Tribe ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, November 5th 2018, 9:36:46 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Scrum-Master-Commercial-Tribe/501885001/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. .</p>

<p>We are now looking for an experienced Scrum Master to join one of our Commercial teams!</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>In your role as a Scrum Master within one of the Commercial teams your mission is to help the team deliver with high velocity and according to plan, that means you need to ensure the speed and delivery. The Commercial teams ensure a smooth journey for Tele2’s customers and develop the functionality needed to enable them to perform their required activities. The Commercial teams are responsible for developing functionality in the different customer lifecycle phases. You will work in close collaboration with the Product Owner (PO) and handle communication with other Stakeholders outside the team. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Leading the team in accordance with Scrum (standups, sprints etc.)</li>
 <li>Taking part in different projects relating to product</li>
 <li>Acting as “Mood-manager” – make sure the team collaborates effectively</li>
 <li>Keeping an eye on velocity (speed of production) within the team</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Your role is roughly composed of 10% strategy and 90% operational tasks. Jira is used as a ticketing system. The system ecosystem is complex and in a constant state of change. You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Scrum Master within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 18 Scrum Masters, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for someone who takes responsibility and dares to take ownership of a critical product within the D&C fauna. We believe that you have good communication skills, are an empathic and pragmatic leader and have a curious mindset. Formal requirements for the role includes:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Experience working as Scrum Master in a large organization</li>
 <li>3+ years experience of team leading, preferably as a Scrum Master</li>
 <li>Preferably experience of an agile transformation</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>The Commercial teams are a collection of different agile teams working directly with customer facing layers for one of these three brands: Comviq, Tele2 Residential and Tele2 Business. In this position you will play a central role in driving the development forward within one of these brands.</p>

<p><strong>Tele2</strong></p>

<p>Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. Tele2 is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) takes initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Planning and Design unit has ownership of all digital products within the digital domain. The unit is responsible for ensuring compliance with the agile way-of-working, IT stack components, supply and resource management and digital architecture</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-501885001-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Scrum Master - Tech Tribe ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, November 5th 2018, 9:36:35 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Scrum-Master-Tech-Tribe/501886701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a forward-thinking Scrum Master to join us!</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>In your role as a Scrum Master within one of our technical teams your mission is to help the team deliver with high velocity and according to plan, that means you need to ensure the speed and delivery. The technical team’s main responsibility is to develop services for other developers, mainly in the commercial teams. The technical teams are responsible for coordinating and solving technical & architectural challenges and provide guidance and simplification. You will work in close collaboration with the Product Owner (PO) and handle communication with Stakeholders outside the team. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Leading the team in accordance with Scrum (standups, sprints etc.)</li>
 <li>Taking part in different projects relating to product</li>
 <li>Acting as “Mood-manager” – make sure the team collaborates effectively</li>
 <li>Keeping an eye on velocity (speed of production) within the team</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Your role is roughly composed of 10% strategy and 90% operational tasks. Jira is used as a ticketing system. The system ecosystem is complex and in a constant state of change. You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Scrum Master within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 18 Scrum Masters, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for someone who takes responsibility and dares to take ownership of a critical product within the Digital and Channels fauna. We believe that you have good communication skills, are an empathic and pragmatic leader and have a curious mindset. Formal requirements for the role includes:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Experience working as Scrum Master in a large organization</li>
 <li>3+ years’ experience of team leading, preferably as a Scrum Master</li>
 <li>Preferably experience of an agile transformation</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>Working as a Scrum Master within D&C you will play a central role in one of these eight agile teams: Comviq Integration, Residential/Business Integration, Common Capabilities, Commerce, Identity & Auth, ER, Self-Care and DevOps/SRE.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>Tele2</strong></p>

<p>Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. Tele2 is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation. For more information visit <u>www.tele2.com</u>.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) takes initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Planning and Design unit has ownership of all digital products within the digital domain. The unit is responsible for ensuring compliance with the agile way-of-working, IT stack component, supply and resource management and digital architecture.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-501886701-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Digital Architect ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, November 5th 2018, 9:36:41 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Digital-Architect/501893701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) takes initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>We’re now looking for a Digital Architect to help us develop world-class IT solutions.</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>As a Digital Architect within D&C SE you work as part of a small team of Digital Architects dedicated to setting and evolving the target architecture as well as our best-practices and patterns. This involves taking on multiple roles and supporting several products and parts of the organization. The major roles you will take on are:</p>

<p>“Venture Architect” - This will be your main focus and will comprise 60-70% of your work. In this role you have the overall responsibility for the technical architecture in the Solutioning process of a given Venture (project). This includes working with a Venture Team – a virtual cross-functional team spanning over multiple domains – to design a solution, and facilitating Venture Refinement – breaking down the solution into smaller deliverables (Features, Epics and Stories). In this role you collaborate closely with the Sponsor Architect (a senior collegue) and have the support of a Solution Architect Counsel (SAC) comprised of four individuals.</p>

<p><br />
“The Mentor” - Support our teams in architectural questions and discussions. Bridge the gap between architecture and implementation by guiding our teams through the different phases of architectural design all the way down to implementation in code.</p>

<p><br />
“The Governor” - Work with setting and evolving our architectural best practices and patterns and evolving our target architecture and digital blueprint. Make sure our products follow and adhere to our target architecture and participate in creating and evolving the process for architectural governances.</p>

<p><br />
“The Educator & Innovator” - Keep up to date on the latest trends within architecture and spread knowledge. Evolve and enhance our strategy and process regarding architecture. Public speaking representing and enhancing our company brand in the Tech-community.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for someone who has a challenger mentalityand dares to take ownership of business-critical processes. In this role you need to be communicative, proactive, and well organized in a fast-paced and dynamic environment. Formal requirements for the role include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years of experience from working as an Architect in a digitalized business</li>
 <li>Excellent facilitation and collaborative architecture skills</li>
 <li>Experience working with agile methodologies</li>
 <li>High-level technical knowledge (on par with a Lead Developer). The technical stack is: Azure, Microservices, .NET, C#, OOP</li>
 <li>Experience using modelling languages such as UML</li>
 <li>Relevant university-level education</li>
</ul>

<p>​</p>

<p>In this role you hold a key position in designing and implementing solutions vital to the future success of Tele2. You work at the very heart of technical development within an agile IT-organization.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-501893701-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Butikschef till Tele2 i Västerås! ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Wednesday, November 7th 2018, 9:37:27 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/V%C3%A4ster%C3%A5s-Butikschef-till-Tele2-i-V%C3%A4ster%C3%A5s%21/502366501/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Vill du vara en del av vår framgångsrika butikskedja? Vi söker nu en Butikschef till Tele2 i Västerås!<br />
<br />
Vi arbetar nära våra kunder och ger service i en bransch som är en stor och viktig del av vardagen. Som Butikschef på Tele2 är du en förebild för dina medarbetare och är duktig på att skapa engagemang och motivation. Tillsammans med ditt team ansvarar du för att leverera den absolut bästa servicen till våra kunder och göra vardagen lite lättare.<br />
<br />
Vi söker dig som har:</p>

<ul>
 <li>minst fem års arbetslivserfarenhet av detaljhandel</li>
 <li>minst ett års erfarenhet av att leda, coacha och följa upp personal</li>
 <li>intresse av dagens teknik</li>
 <li>fullständig gymnasieutbildning och goda engelskkunskaper. Behärskar du fler språk är det givetvis en fördel</li>
 <li>telekomerfarenhet är meriterande<br />
 </li>
</ul>

<p>Som Butikschef har du det övergripande ansvaret för den dagliga driften av butiken. Du driver försäljning genom att inspirera och utveckla våra duktiga säljare så att de blir riktigt proffsiga i mötet med kund. Som person tror vi därför att du är en coachande och inspirerande ledare som har stor förmåga att arbeta strukturerat efter uppsatta mål. Du är duktig på försäljning och brinner för att se dina medarbetare utvecklas.</p>

<p>Vi erbjuder dig en spännande och utvecklande roll i en miljö där du har möjlighet att göra skillnad. Vi har en familjär stämning och med teamet i ryggen får du det bästa utgångsläget för att få butiken att prestera på topp.</p>

<p>Vi drivs av intern utveckling och för den som har ambition och vilja ser vi detta som en start för en karriär på Tele2. Som Butikschef erbjuds du en gedigen introduktion samt vårt skräddarsydda ledarskapsprogram för att göra dig mer rustad inför att ta din butik till nya höjder!</p>

<p>Tjänsten är en tillsvidareanställning på heltid med placering i Igor, Västerås. </p>

<p>Skicka in din ansökan redan idag, då vi kommer att kalla till intervjuer löpande.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan!</p>

<p>Vi begär utdrag ur belastningsregistret på alla vi anställer.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Sales]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-U]]></state><city><![CDATA[Västerås]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-502366501-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Administratör Access Registration på Tele2! ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, November 19th 2018, 10:37:28 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Administrat%C3%B6r-Access-Registration-p%C3%A5-Tele2%21/504487601/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[Administratör till Access Registration på Tele2!

<p>Vill du arbeta med orderadministration i en spännande och föränderlig bransch där kommunikation står i centrum? Vi söker nu en serviceinriktad och strukturerad Administratör till vår avdelning Access Registration på Tele2!</p>

<p>Access Registration är en del av Tele2´s implementationsorganisation som bl.a. säkerställer att våra kundavtal registreras korrekt i order- och faktureringssystem och är en viktig funktion för att vi ska hålla en hög kvalitet i vår kundleverans. Vi söker nu en Administratör som kommer att ingå i ett team om 10 personer och som arbetar med orderregistrering.</p>

<p>I ditt arbete som Administratör har du nyckelroll i bolaget mellan sälj- och implementationsverksamheten. Du har ett nära samarbete med kundansvariga inom Tele2s företagsförsäljning och säkerställer att kundorder är kompletta och rätt registrerade i våra system, vilket skapar förutsättningar för att leverans och fakturering till våra kunder blir korrekt och i enlighet med avtalen. De system vi huvudsakligen arbetar i är Melody och Navibilling. Det är en självklarhet att du förstår och lever efter våra värderingar – öppenhet, kostnadsmedvetenhet och flexibilitet.</p>

<p><strong>Dina huvudsakliga arbetsuppgifter är att:</strong></p>

<ul>
 <li>Ta emot beställningar från kunder, säljare och kundservice avseende datatjänster (Internet/IP VPN)</li>
 <li>Assistera säljare med accessförfrågningar vid större affärer</li>
 <li>Bevakning av ärenden i gemensamma maillådor avseende kundfrågor, fakturaärenden, tilläggsbeställningar m.m.</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Vi söker dig som har:</strong></p>

<ul>
 <li>Minst ett års erfarenhet av liknande uppgifter</li>
 <li>Vana av att jobba i komplexa system</li>
 <li>Mycket goda kunskaper i Office-paketet</li>
 <li>Mycket goda kunskaper i såväl svenska som engelska i tal och skrift</li>
</ul>

<p>Som person är du strukturerad, effektiv, noggrann och har sinne för administration. Du gillar att ha många kontakter i ditt arbete och håller hög service- och kvalitetsnivå mot våra kunder och vår säljkår, även i stundtals tidspressade situationer, men kan också ställa krav och vara tydlig i din kommunikation. Du tar ansvar för ditt arbete och arbetar självständigt. Vidare är du nyfiken, intresserad och har inställningen att problem är till för att lösas.</p>

<p>Tjänsten är placerad på vårt huvudkontor i <strong>Kista.</strong> Välkommen med din ansökan, dock senast den <strong>16 december </strong>2018. Urval och intervjuer sker löpande.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Administration]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Kista]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504487601-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend Developer - Comviq Integration squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, November 20th 2018, 5:37:44 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer-Comviq-Integration-squad/504680301/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.<br />
 </p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET developer to the Comviq Integration squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a backend developer within the Comviq Integration squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. The squads main mission is to provide resilient and fast endpoints with great usability for developers within the Comviq product, enabling the business to run fast. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification</li>
</ul>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a backend developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 backend developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over their code and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>Working in the Comviq Integration squad you will have lots of touch-points within Tele2 and the Comviq product. As a backend developer in this squad you will develop best-in-class developer experience for the users of the Comviq product.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504680301-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend Developer - Residential/Business Integration squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, November 20th 2018, 5:37:21 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer-ResidentialBusiness-Integration-squad/504680901/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.<br />
 </p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET developer to the Residential / Business Integration squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Backend Developer within the Residential / Business Integration squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. The squads mission is to enable developers by providing fast, reliable and easy to use interfaces, so they can create value to their end users. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a backend developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 backend developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over their code and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>Working in the Residential / Business Integration squad you work with modern products undergoing constant development. These products are business critical and therefore highly prioritized. As a backend developer in this squad you will develop best-in-class developer experience for the users of the API: s.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504680901-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Residential Orientation squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, November 20th 2018, 4:37:53 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-End-developer-Residential-Orientation-squad/504684301/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services, and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-End developer who wants to deliver engaging experiences!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Residential Orientation squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The Residential Orientation squad's mission is to give potential customers access to relevant and engaging information, with the aim of enabling a smooth and natural transition towards the customer journeys. In this role you will collaborate closely with other teams when needed. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-End developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include: <br />
 </p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The Residential Orientation squad is responsible for Tele2's digital interface and this gives the squad great opportunities to develop- and always use new methods and tools. Since the Orientation Squad also is Venture (project) owner for all campaigns, working as a Front-End developer will give you a central role where you will build things that thousands of visitors per minute will see.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504684301-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Comviq Use squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Tuesday, November 20th 2018, 4:38:30 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-End-developer-Comviq-Use-squad/504687001/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services, and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-End developer who wants to deliver world-class user experiences to customers!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Comviq Use squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The Comviq Use squad is responsible for services regarding the App, the existing customer stock and services regarding customers with prepaid phone cards. The squad works with different types of platforms and techniques. In this role you will collaborate closely with other teams when needed. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-End developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include: </p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The squad is responsible for a large number of customers which means that even minor changes affect lots of people. Working in the Comviq Use squad will give you a central role within a critical product.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504687001-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-end Developer ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Wednesday, November 21st 2018, 4:37:45 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-end-Developer/504836701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Business Use/Get Help squad

<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services, and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-End developer who wants to deliver world-class user experiences to customers!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Business Use/Get Help squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The Squad help existing customers within the B2B segment. The squad is responsible to help customers with their day-to-day management such as monthly data consumption and support customers regarding invoice management. The Business Use/Get help squad are responsible for the B2B customers both on the webpage and in the App. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-End developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include: </p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The squad is new within the Commercial Tribe works with a newly build codebase. Joining the Tele2 Business Use/Get help squad in this stadium you will have a key role within the team.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504836701-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Comviq Orientation squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Wednesday, November 21st 2018, 4:37:51 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-End-developer-Comviq-Orientation-squad/504837801/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services, and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-End developer who wants to deliver world-class user experiences to our customers!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Comviq Orientation squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The Comviq Orientation squads mission is to make visitors on comviq.se feel a strong connection to the brand. The squad is responsible for creating a smooth transfer within the customer journey and make it easy to search and find the information the visitors need. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-End developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include: <br />
 </p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The squad does a lot of creative work that is highly visible for all visitors at comviq.se. Working as a Front-End developer within the Comviq Orientation quad will give you a central role within a critical product.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504837801-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, November 22nd 2018, 10:40:15 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-DevOps-Engineer/504913601/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p><strong>DevOps Engineer</strong><br />
<br />
Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p><br />
The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our public web, commercial and self-service solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Quality and Operations unit is responsible for system management and QA within the D&C-domain. The unit is composed of Quality Assurance Engineers, Incident & Problem Managers and DevOps.</p>

<p>We are looking for a DevOps Engineer with a background from development who doesn’t think great is good enough!<br />
<br />
<strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>As a DevOps Engineer you will work with implementing and maintaining the right tools for D&C to ensure smooth and seamless IT-deliveries with high quality. This is done by standardizing processes, stabilizing infrastructure, enabling automation and reducing human intervention. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Cloud infrastructure: Automation, configuration, deployment, monitoring</li>
 <li>CI/CD: Automated build, test and deployment of applications and services.</li>
 <li>Site Reliability: Design for operational quality, monitoring and maintenance</li>
 <li>Monitoring and sanity checks of IT-services, using metrics to improve performance and quality</li>
 <li>Catering for data driven operational insights</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a DevOps Engineer within D&C you are also a part of various forums meeting on a regular basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.<br />
<br />
<strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>As a Dev Ops Engineer within D&C you need to be technically skilled, preferably you have experience working as a developer and from operations. In this role you are responsible for the digital development logistics from start to finish as well as for operational IT-services and it is up to you to make sure you are one step ahead. You enjoy responsibility and you are skilled at communicating your ideas to stakeholders. Formal requirements for the role include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>2+ years’ experience working as a developer</li>
 <li>Experience from implementing and maintaining CI/CD pipelines</li>
 <li>Experience in utilizing metrics to drive improvements</li>
 <li>Experience in cloud environments (preferably Azure)</li>
 <li>Experience in presenting business- and technically-oriented</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
As a DevOps Engineer within D&C you will be part of an agile team so being a team player and living our values is essential and key for us to deliver high quality cost efficient IT-services.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504913601-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Java Developer ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, November 22nd 2018, 2:38:17 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Java-Developer/504943101/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The IT Business to Business SE (IT B2B) unit is responsible for the delivery of IT solutions to the Commercial Business unit. The purpose is to streamline the management of Tele2's large and small business clients such as Nordea, Polisen, PostNord, Skatteverket and Stockholms stad. This is done by offering the end-user comprehensive digital interfaces and automating internal processes, so that they are smooth and effective.</p>

<p>The IT B2B systems make the base of several of Tele2's customer commitments, including automated mobile and network deliveries as well as subcontracting.</p>

<p>We’re looking for a passionate Java Developer who wants to create world-class B2B services!</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p>As a Java Developer within the IT B2B unit you will you will work in the Java team. The team is responsible for developing systems for network deliveries and customer web sites. The role places high demands on you as a developer to get to understand the systems quickly and in addition to good knowledge of the system, even in one area, the opportunities will be great. We would like to see you become a Lead Developer or Architect over time. Formal responsibilities include:<br />
 </p>

<ul>
 <li>Work with all phases of the development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support</li>
 <li>Work as part of a cross-functional team to understand business needs and requirements</li>
 <li>Be up to date with new technologies and implement them when needed</li>
 <li>Keep the development on track and work after best practice</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: Javabased Microservice- environment, Java 10, Spring, Spring Boot, TypeScript, Angular, Intellij IDEA, Maven, Git and GitLab, VMW, Kubernetes and Docker.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person who takes initiatives and are skilled at solving problems in a creative way. We believe you have a genuine interest for new technologies and development and you have the ability to work in a fast- paced environment both individually and in teams. We believe you have an eye for details and always strive to deliver high end quality. Formal requirements include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>5+ years’ experience working as a software developer</li>
 <li>Experience working with Java, Spring and JavaScript</li>
 <li>Experience working with Linux/Unix/Mac</li>
 <li>Excellent communication skills in both Swedish and English</li>
</ul>

<p>The team consists of developers and architects that together are responsible for design, development and integration within one system area each. We work according to scrum with three teams delivering new releases every third week. In order to share experiences and always be updated in new technologies, the unit hold regular competence forums and tech talks.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.<br />
 </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504943101-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET developer ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, November 22nd 2018, 4:38:08 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Full-Stack-_NET-developer/504959201/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com</p>

<p>The IT Business to Business SE (IT B2B) unit is responsible for the delivery of IT solutions to the Commercial Business unit. The purpose is to streamline the management of Tele2's large and small business clients such as Nordea, Polisen, PostNord, Skatteverket and Stockholms stad. This is done by offering the end-user comprehensive digital interfaces and automating internal processes, so that they are smooth and effective. </p>

<p>The IT B2B systems make the base of several of Tele2's customer commitments, including automated mobile and network deliveries as well as subcontracting. </p>

<p>We’re looking for a passionate Full Stack .NET developer who wants to create world- class B2B services!</p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p><br />
As a Full Stack .NET developer within the IT B2B unit you will you will work in the .NET team. The team is responsible for developing systems for order and delivery management. You will participate in all stages of the development life-cycle such as requirements analysis, design, development, testing and implementation. Formal responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new products</li>
 <li>Provide information and support when required</li>
 <li>Provide technical troubleshooting and debug support</li>
 <li>Evaluate new design proposals, and investigate and recommend solutions and process improvements</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET / .NET Core, C#, TypeScript, MVC and SQL (SQL Server), Visual Studio, GIT and Team City.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person who takes initiatives and are skilled at solving problems in a creative way. We believe you have a genuine interest for new technologies and development and you have the ability to work in a fast- paced environment both individually and in teams. We believe you have an eye for details and always strive to deliver high end quality. Formal requirements include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>5+ years’ experience working as a .NET backend developer</li>
 <li>Experience working with C#, MVC and T-SQL (SQL Server)</li>
 <li>Excellent communication skills in both Swedish and English</li>
</ul>

<p>The team consists of developers and architects that together are responsible for design, development and integration within one system area each. We work according to scrum with three teams delivering new releases every third week. In order to share experiences and always be updated in new technologies, the unit hold regular competence forums and tech talks.</p>

<p><br />
<strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-504959201-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Domain Architect - BSS Order Management ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Monday, November 26th 2018, 10:39:01 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Domain-Architect-BSS-Order-Management/505183601/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[Domain Architect - BSS OM

<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Order Management Domain within IT Services is one of the key function in the Business Supporting Systems department. In cooperation with our partners the domain is responsible for Orders and Products target architecture planning, maintaining and delivering products to Tele2 countries.</p>

<p> <br />
We are looking for a hands- on Domain Architect with telecom BSS solutions experience! </p>

<p><strong>Role Description</strong></p>

<p><br />
As a Domain Architect within the BSS Order Management Domain you will act as Design Authority in the context of large program deliveries and maintain Solution Knowledge within the respective Domain. You will design and facilitate introduction of architecture for your functional domain to meet business requirements. In this role you will coach and support Solution Architects, Project Managers and other member of the teams, in the framework of developments and projects. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Focus on execution plan in the framework of large projects and control the deliverables from the outsourcing partner</li>
 <li>Define the Design Principles & Patterns for the Solutions in scope</li>
 <li>Act as speaking partner for the BSS Domain and to align with Enterprise Architects, other Domain Architects and Solution Designers</li>
 <li>Support the domain manager in vendor mgmt. activities as solution expert</li>
 <li>Drive innovation in technology</li>
</ul>

<p style="margin-left:48.0px"> </p>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced environment and interact with multiple stakeholders. In this role you will work closely with the development and operations teams.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you with a minimum of 10 years IT experience of designing and integrating telecom BSS solutions related to Order Management, Billing, Telecom CRM, and Service Fulfillment. You need to have a deep understanding of business integration issues and technologies and have an interest of modern technology frameworks. We believe you have a strategic mindset, the capacity to influence and engage and a “big-picture” view to ensuring overall cohesive environment and cross-product architectural alignment. Formal requirements include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Knowledge of designing and implementing Order & Product Management architecture for telecoms</li>
 <li>Knowledge of Integration platforms and Service Delivery solutions</li>
 <li>Experience with Catalog-Driven Order Management</li>
 <li>Experience with IT service providers (on-shore and off-shore) and in the agile way of working</li>
 <li>Ability to educate all parties of the solution, keeping track of the delivery and making sure it happens as per design</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
In this role you will work hands- on and recommend the most appropriate solutions for complex projects, and you define the transition path from current IT stack to target vision and control its correct execution during projects/programs roll-out. You will play a key role within Tele2.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you?</strong><br />
 </p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply with your resume by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-505183601-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Säljare till Tele2 i Nordstan! ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Friday, November 30th 2018, 8:38:15 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/G%C3%B6teborg-S%C3%A4ljare-till-Tele2-i-Nordstan%21/505808001/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Vill du vara en del av vår framgångsrika butikskedja? Vi söker nu en säljare till Tele2-butiken i Nordstan, Göteborg!</p>

<p>Vi arbetar nära våra kunder och ger service i en bransch som är en stor och viktig del av vardagen. Som butikssäljare på Tele2 ansvarar du för att leverera den absolut bästa servicen till våra kunder och samtidigt göra vardagen lite lättare.</p>

<p><b>Vi söker dig </b>som har<b> </b>tidigare erfarenhet av serviceyrken och ett stort intresse av dagens teknik. Som person är du social, resultatinriktad och har ett brinnande intresse för försäljning och kundservice.</p>

<p><b>Vi erbjuder dig </b>en spännande och utvecklande roll i en miljö där du dagligen gör skillnad för våra kunder. Vi har en familjär stämning och med teamet i ryggen får du det bästa utgångsläget för att prestera på topp. På Tele2 drivs vi av intern utveckling och för rätt person finns det goda utvecklingsmöjligheter inom butikerna. Som nyanställd erbjuds du en gedigen introduktion för att göra dig mer rustad inför butiksjobbet.</p>

<p>Tjänsten är ett vikariat på heltid med placering i Nordstan, Göteborg. För rätt person finns god möjlighet till förlängning.</p>

<p>Är du en Tele2:are? Vill du ta plats i en flexibel, prestigelös organisation som präglas av en stark teamkänsla, högt engagemang och mycket glädje? Skicka in din ansökan redan idag, då vi kommer att kalla till intervjuer löpande.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan!</p>

<p>Vi begär utdrag ur belastningsregistret på alla vi anställer.</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Sales]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-O]]></state><city><![CDATA[Göteborg]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-505808001-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend Developer - ER squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 6th 2018, 10:37:13 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer-ER-squad/506513201/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.<br>
 </p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET Backend Developer to the ER squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a .NET Backend Developer within the ER squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. The squad provide support, perspective and coordination for all squads within Tele2’s digital channels to ensure smooth and efficient processes when solving complex issues. The squad suggest improvements in architecture and solutions to create scalability, stability and reusability in Tele2’s digital channels. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification</li>
</ul>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a backend developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 Backend Developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over their code and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>The ER squad participate in new and innovative initiatives and projects and has a great impact and on improvement measures in the form of proactive problem management. As a .NET Backend Developer within the ER squad you will be a central part of a "go-to-squad" who is able to offer expertise in difficult and complex problems.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-506513201-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend Developer - Commerce Capabilities squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 6th 2018, 11:36:48 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer-Commerce-Capabilities-squad/506520501/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.<br />
 </p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET Backend Developer to the Commerce Capabilities squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a .NET Backend Developer within the Commerce Capabilities squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. The squad has the responsibility to develop and maintain the SalesOrderEngine and its services. SalesOrderEngine is the order engine of the new commerce platform. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification</li>
</ul>

<p><br />
You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a .NET Backend Developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 Backend Developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over their code and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>Working in the Commerce Capabilities squad gives you the opportunity to work with modern products and techniques. The SalesOrderEngine is built on a new architecture that utilizes Microsoft Azure as cloud service, and this gives you as a Backend Developer the opportunity to work with a product that doesn't have a long legacy.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-506520501-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[.NET Backend Developer - Common Capabilities squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 6th 2018, 11:36:27 am]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-_NET-Backend-Developer-Common-Capabilities-squad/506522201/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.<br />
 </p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a skilled .NET Backend Developer to the Common Capabilities squad!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a .NET Backend Developer within the Common Capabilities squad you work with all phases of software development life cycle, including analysis, design, code review, testing and support. The squads main task is to build common and generic microservices that are shared by all brands within tele2. The aim is to enable developers in other squads to realize their ideas in a simple, reliable and effective way. Your responsibilities include:<br />
 </p>

<ul>
 <li>Writing reusable, testable, and efficient code</li>
 <li>Research and implement new technologies as needed</li>
 <li>Keep development projects on track, on time, and on specification<br />
 </li>
</ul>

<p>You will work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Backend Developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of 23 Backend Developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for you who have the ability to take ownership over their code and are comfortable working under tight deadlines. You are great at working with diverse teams and have experience working with a scrum-based delivery. Formal qualifications include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years experience working as a .NET Developer</li>
 <li>Experience working in a distributed solution landscape (Microservices oriented, multilayer solution design)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: .NET 4.6, SQL (MS SQL/Oracle), Visual Studio 2015+, MVC, GIT, JavaScript, NuGet, SCRUM, Apigee</p>

<p>The Common Capabilities squad will be facing new exciting challenges. Several projects will be rebuilt in .NET Core and will be based in Azure with automated scaling and higher resilience, in line with the new target architecture. In this position you will play a key role in the development of these new microservices.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-506522201-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Front-End developer - Comviq Join squad ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 6th 2018, 4:37:05 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Kista-Front-End-developer-Comviq-Join-squad/506575901/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 is one of Europe's fastest growing Telecom operators offering mobile services, fixed broadband and telephony, data network services, content services, and global IoT solutions. Every day 17 million customers across 8 countries enjoy a fast and wireless experience through our award-winning networks. Tele2 was founded in 1993 and is listed on the NASDAQ OMX Stockholm. Tele2 has around 6000 employees with offices in the Nordics and Baltics. For more information visit www.tele2.com.</p>

<p>The Digitals & Channels SE unit (D&C) runs initiatives for the IT- and digital products in Sweden, for example our commerce, self-service, identity and branding solutions. Together with the Commercial and Marketing teams we develop new products - from start to finish. We create services that bring value to our customers and help us achieve our business goals.</p>

<p>The Digital Production unit within D&C is responsible for competence- and resource centres divided into different technology areas. The areas are: integration development, capability development, channel development and UX & design production.</p>

<p>We are now looking for a Front-end developer who wants to deliver world-class user experiences to customers!</p>

<p><strong>Role description </strong></p>

<p>As a Front-End developer within the Comviq Join squad you will be responsible for building great customer experiences. The squad support new customers from when they show purchase interest until their service is in use. The squad ensure that customers have a good experience all the way from when they looking to buy one of our products and commit to a purchase, to when they actually receive their product and start using it. In this role you will collaborate closely with other teams when needed. 80% of your role will focus on development and 20% with demo and retro refinement. Your responsibilities include:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Develop and implement new user-facing features</li>
 <li>Maintaining and improving our website</li>
 <li>Discuss design and UX (with the team) before implementation</li>
 <li>Ensure that our customer’s experience is the best it can be</li>
</ul>

<p>You work in a fast-paced, dynamic and forward-thinking environment. As a Front-End developer within D&C you are also a part of a chapter, composed of nine Front-end developers, meeting on a weekly basis to share knowledge and exchange thoughts and ideas.</p>

<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>

<p>We are looking for a person with strong web development and analytical skills who has the ability to prioritize, plan and take ownership of their work. We believe you have interest in how the UX design affects your work and have a strong desire to learn new things at all times. You are comfortable working under tight deadlines and have the ability to work independently as well as collaborate effectively with others. Formal qualifications include: </p>

<ul>
 <li>3+ years’ experience working as a Front-End developer</li>
 <li>Documented experience working with GIT</li>
 <li>Experience working with web accessibility (WCAG)</li>
</ul>

<p>Technologies and methodologies used include: AngularJS, Object oriented JavaScript, MVC Razor View (Epi), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Front-end-optimizing, SEO, NodeJS, Gulp, Windows server environment.</p>

<p>The squad continuously test and evaluate how to improve our purchase flow, working in Comviq Join squad you get to pitch and test your ideas to make the product the best. Working in the purchase flow, we get to see exactly how the changes we make impact Tele2’s business.</p>

<p><strong>Does this sound like a suitable challenge for you? </strong></p>

<p>If so - we look forward to receiving your application! Please apply by the link below. Selection and interviews are conducted continuously. </p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Stockholm]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-506575901-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Leveransledare Datanät inom B2B och Wholesale ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 13th 2018, 5:36:49 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Leveransledare-Datan%C3%A4t-inom-B2B-och-Wholesale/507046701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 är ett internationellt bolag med helhetslösningar inom IT och telekom till företag, privatpersoner och organisationer där lösningarna ska bidra till utveckling av effektivitet, relationer och affärer. Vi har utmanaranda i vårt DNA. Vi utmanar våra konkurrenter och marknaden förstås, men framförallt oss själva. Vi verkar på en marknad som ständigt växer och förändras. Våra kunder vill ständigt ha nya och bättre lösningar vilket ställer höga krav på oss. Självklart vill vi möta dessa krav, därför blir hur vi arbetar och vilka vi är vår nyckel till framgång. </p>

<p>Nu söker vi en leveransledare för en visstidsanställning på 6 månader till vår grupp Network Implementation Management inom avdelningen B2B Delivery. Gruppen ansvarar för leveransledning samt projektering av våra datanätstjänster inom B2B och Wholesale.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vi och jobbet...</strong></p>

<p>Network Implementation Management ansvarar för att med kvalitet och med precision leveransleda samt projektera Tele2:s datanätstjänster inom Business och Wholesalesegmentet. Gruppen är ett tight och fokuserat team med högt engagemang och stort kundfokus. Vi är garanten för att våra kunder får en trygg och träffsäker leverans. Vår styrka är vårt synkroniserade lagspel, där vi kompletterar varandra och har riktigt kul ihop!</p>

<p>Som leveransledare är du kundens kontaktperson igenom hela leveransen. Du hanterar nya leveranser baserade på kopparaccesser och trådlösa mobila lösningar. Du hanterar även uppgraderingar och tilläggsbeställningar för våra befintliga kunder. Vidare säkerställer du och tidsbokar resurser, interna och externa. Du dokumenterar leveransprogress i våra stödsystem och koordinerar övriga delar såsom leveranstekniker och underentreprenörer. Du är med kunden under hela leveransen för att säkerställa att vi har en nöjd kund efter driftsatt tjänst.</p>

<p>Denna del av leveransledningsteamet präglas av hög och snabb genomströmning av leveranser.</p>

<p>Du kommer att ha många kontaktytor och kommunicera med såväl kunder som andra avdelningar internt på Tele2.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vad du har...</strong></p>

<p>Kvalifikationer</p>

<ul>
 <li>Bakgrund från en operatör eller leveransledning från annat område.</li>
 <li>Teknisk bakgrund från datakommunikationsområdet är meriterande.</li>
 <li>Då våra kundkontakter sker på både svenska och engelska ska du obehindrat kunna hantera dessa kontakter i både tal och skrift</li>
</ul>

<p>Egenskaper</p>

<p>Vårt arbetssätt präglas av Teamwork, ansvar, öppenhet och prestigelöshet. För att trivas i vårt team är det därför viktigt att:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Du är riktigt passionerad av att göra kunden nöjd!</li>
 <li>Du som person är en utåtriktad problemlösare, som känner ägandeskap för leveransen och kundnöjdhet</li>
 <li>Du är stresstålig och noggrann även i pressade situationer</li>
 <li>Du är en lagspelare och arbetar i grupp på ett prestigelöst sätt, alltid villig att hjälpa dina kollegor där det behövs</li>
</ul>

<p>Tjänsten är en visstidsanställning på 6 månader med placeringsort Kista, Malmö eller Göteborg.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan senast den 16 december 2018. Urval och intervjuer sker löpande!</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-O]]></state><city><![CDATA[Göteborg]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-507046701-ADGEN_TELE2-1]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Leveransledare Datanät inom B2B och Wholesale ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 13th 2018, 5:36:49 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Leveransledare-Datan%C3%A4t-inom-B2B-och-Wholesale/507046701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 är ett internationellt bolag med helhetslösningar inom IT och telekom till företag, privatpersoner och organisationer där lösningarna ska bidra till utveckling av effektivitet, relationer och affärer. Vi har utmanaranda i vårt DNA. Vi utmanar våra konkurrenter och marknaden förstås, men framförallt oss själva. Vi verkar på en marknad som ständigt växer och förändras. Våra kunder vill ständigt ha nya och bättre lösningar vilket ställer höga krav på oss. Självklart vill vi möta dessa krav, därför blir hur vi arbetar och vilka vi är vår nyckel till framgång. </p>

<p>Nu söker vi en leveransledare för en visstidsanställning på 6 månader till vår grupp Network Implementation Management inom avdelningen B2B Delivery. Gruppen ansvarar för leveransledning samt projektering av våra datanätstjänster inom B2B och Wholesale.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vi och jobbet...</strong></p>

<p>Network Implementation Management ansvarar för att med kvalitet och med precision leveransleda samt projektera Tele2:s datanätstjänster inom Business och Wholesalesegmentet. Gruppen är ett tight och fokuserat team med högt engagemang och stort kundfokus. Vi är garanten för att våra kunder får en trygg och träffsäker leverans. Vår styrka är vårt synkroniserade lagspel, där vi kompletterar varandra och har riktigt kul ihop!</p>

<p>Som leveransledare är du kundens kontaktperson igenom hela leveransen. Du hanterar nya leveranser baserade på kopparaccesser och trådlösa mobila lösningar. Du hanterar även uppgraderingar och tilläggsbeställningar för våra befintliga kunder. Vidare säkerställer du och tidsbokar resurser, interna och externa. Du dokumenterar leveransprogress i våra stödsystem och koordinerar övriga delar såsom leveranstekniker och underentreprenörer. Du är med kunden under hela leveransen för att säkerställa att vi har en nöjd kund efter driftsatt tjänst.</p>

<p>Denna del av leveransledningsteamet präglas av hög och snabb genomströmning av leveranser.</p>

<p>Du kommer att ha många kontaktytor och kommunicera med såväl kunder som andra avdelningar internt på Tele2.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vad du har...</strong></p>

<p>Kvalifikationer</p>

<ul>
 <li>Bakgrund från en operatör eller leveransledning från annat område.</li>
 <li>Teknisk bakgrund från datakommunikationsområdet är meriterande.</li>
 <li>Då våra kundkontakter sker på både svenska och engelska ska du obehindrat kunna hantera dessa kontakter i både tal och skrift</li>
</ul>

<p>Egenskaper</p>

<p>Vårt arbetssätt präglas av Teamwork, ansvar, öppenhet och prestigelöshet. För att trivas i vårt team är det därför viktigt att:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Du är riktigt passionerad av att göra kunden nöjd!</li>
 <li>Du som person är en utåtriktad problemlösare, som känner ägandeskap för leveransen och kundnöjdhet</li>
 <li>Du är stresstålig och noggrann även i pressade situationer</li>
 <li>Du är en lagspelare och arbetar i grupp på ett prestigelöst sätt, alltid villig att hjälpa dina kollegor där det behövs</li>
</ul>

<p>Tjänsten är en visstidsanställning på 6 månader med placeringsort Kista, Malmö eller Göteborg.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan senast den 16 december 2018. Urval och intervjuer sker löpande!</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-AB]]></state><city><![CDATA[Kista]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-507046701-ADGEN_TELE2-2]]></referencenumber></job><job><title><![CDATA[Leveransledare Datanät inom B2B och Wholesale ]]></title><date><![CDATA[Thursday, December 13th 2018, 5:36:49 pm]]></date><url><![CDATA[https://jobs.tele2.com/job/Stockholm-Leveransledare-Datan%C3%A4t-inom-B2B-och-Wholesale/507046701/]]></url><company><![CDATA[Tele2]]></company><sourcename><![CDATA[Tele2]]></sourcename><description><![CDATA[<p>Tele2 är ett internationellt bolag med helhetslösningar inom IT och telekom till företag, privatpersoner och organisationer där lösningarna ska bidra till utveckling av effektivitet, relationer och affärer. Vi har utmanaranda i vårt DNA. Vi utmanar våra konkurrenter och marknaden förstås, men framförallt oss själva. Vi verkar på en marknad som ständigt växer och förändras. Våra kunder vill ständigt ha nya och bättre lösningar vilket ställer höga krav på oss. Självklart vill vi möta dessa krav, därför blir hur vi arbetar och vilka vi är vår nyckel till framgång. </p>

<p>Nu söker vi en leveransledare för en visstidsanställning på 6 månader till vår grupp Network Implementation Management inom avdelningen B2B Delivery. Gruppen ansvarar för leveransledning samt projektering av våra datanätstjänster inom B2B och Wholesale.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vi och jobbet...</strong></p>

<p>Network Implementation Management ansvarar för att med kvalitet och med precision leveransleda samt projektera Tele2:s datanätstjänster inom Business och Wholesalesegmentet. Gruppen är ett tight och fokuserat team med högt engagemang och stort kundfokus. Vi är garanten för att våra kunder får en trygg och träffsäker leverans. Vår styrka är vårt synkroniserade lagspel, där vi kompletterar varandra och har riktigt kul ihop!</p>

<p>Som leveransledare är du kundens kontaktperson igenom hela leveransen. Du hanterar nya leveranser baserade på kopparaccesser och trådlösa mobila lösningar. Du hanterar även uppgraderingar och tilläggsbeställningar för våra befintliga kunder. Vidare säkerställer du och tidsbokar resurser, interna och externa. Du dokumenterar leveransprogress i våra stödsystem och koordinerar övriga delar såsom leveranstekniker och underentreprenörer. Du är med kunden under hela leveransen för att säkerställa att vi har en nöjd kund efter driftsatt tjänst.</p>

<p>Denna del av leveransledningsteamet präglas av hög och snabb genomströmning av leveranser.</p>

<p>Du kommer att ha många kontaktytor och kommunicera med såväl kunder som andra avdelningar internt på Tele2.</p>

<p><strong>Det här är vad du har...</strong></p>

<p>Kvalifikationer</p>

<ul>
 <li>Bakgrund från en operatör eller leveransledning från annat område.</li>
 <li>Teknisk bakgrund från datakommunikationsområdet är meriterande.</li>
 <li>Då våra kundkontakter sker på både svenska och engelska ska du obehindrat kunna hantera dessa kontakter i både tal och skrift</li>
</ul>

<p>Egenskaper</p>

<p>Vårt arbetssätt präglas av Teamwork, ansvar, öppenhet och prestigelöshet. För att trivas i vårt team är det därför viktigt att:</p>

<ul>
 <li>Du är riktigt passionerad av att göra kunden nöjd!</li>
 <li>Du som person är en utåtriktad problemlösare, som känner ägandeskap för leveransen och kundnöjdhet</li>
 <li>Du är stresstålig och noggrann även i pressade situationer</li>
 <li>Du är en lagspelare och arbetar i grupp på ett prestigelöst sätt, alltid villig att hjälpa dina kollegor där det behövs</li>
</ul>

<p>Tjänsten är en visstidsanställning på 6 månader med placeringsort Kista, Malmö eller Göteborg.</p>

<p>Välkommen med din ansökan senast den 16 december 2018. Urval och intervjuer sker löpande!</p>]]></description><jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype><category><![CDATA[Data & IT]]></category><email><![CDATA[hr-support-se@tele2.com]]></email><country><![CDATA[SE]]></country><state><![CDATA[SE-M]]></state><city><![CDATA[Malmö]]></city><referencenumber><![CDATA[adway-507046701-ADGEN_TELE2-3]]></referencenumber></job></source>